[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company filed for bankruptcy in May 2009 and was partially bought by the US Government to keep production?", "correct_answer": "General Motors", "incorrect_answers": ["General Electric", "General Beton", "General Paper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original version of Father of the Bride arrived in theaters in 1950. What was the title of its 1951 sequel?", "correct_answer": "Fathers Little Dividend", "incorrect_answers": ["Life with Baby!", "Full Circle", "Father of the Bride Part II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement regarding Butterfly McQueens death is true?", "correct_answer": "She died at the age of 84 in Augusta, Georgia.", "incorrect_answers": ["She died at the age of 94 in Los Angeles, California.", "She died of pneumonia at 77 in her home in Bramwell, South Carolina.", "She died poverty stricken at the age of 74, in New York City."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the 27the amendment to the U.S. Constitution ratified?", "correct_answer": "1992", "incorrect_answers": ["1971", "1920", "1865"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the movie Sleepless in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "Nora Ephron", "incorrect_answers": ["Rob Reiner", "Penny Marshall", "Gary Marshall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Toyotas first widely available gas-electric hybrid car?", "correct_answer": "Prius", "incorrect_answers": ["Celica", "Camry", "Insight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the original version of Layla by Derek and the Dominoes, the guitar riffs were played by these two men.", "correct_answer": "Eric Clapton and Duane Allman", "incorrect_answers": ["Eric Clapton and George Harrison", "Eric Clapton and Carl Radle", "Eric Clapton and Bobby Whitlock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the parrots breeding habits?", "correct_answer": "Parrots are monogamous.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Parrots are polygamous.", "Parrots are polyandrous."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn is the Roman name of the Greek Titan Cronus. Who is Cronus son?", "correct_answer": "Zeus", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Apollo", "Hera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Danny Zuko, one of the main characters in the movie Grease, received a lettermans sweater  for which sport?", "correct_answer": "Track", "incorrect_answers": ["Basketball", "Baseball", "Wrestling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does Ben Wade kill Byron McElroy in 3:10 to Yuma?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Because he never knew when to shut up", "Because he insulted his mother", "To escape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Toco Toucans strange appearance is due this.", "correct_answer": "Its bill", "incorrect_answers": ["Its movement", "Its eyes", "Its feathers"]}]